A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20 FA292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Files, 1920-1993; 2; 242 Box(es)
  - Haddow, Thomas - 1948 - Scotland - Business Administration, 1948-1987 (Box 84, Folder 687)
  - Haffenden, Philip Spencer - 1955 - England - American Colonial History, 1955-1986 (Box 84, Folder 688)
  - Haggard, Patrick Neville - 1987 - England - Psychology, 1986-1991 (Box 84, Folder 689)
  - Haggard, Stephen Doveton - 1985 - England - Museum Studies, 1984-1990 (Box 84, Folder 690)
  - Haig, David - 1948 - England - Virology, 1948-1987 (Box 84, Folder 691)
  - Halcrow, John Morrison - 1958 - England - American Education and Journalism, 1958-1986 (Box 85, Folder 692)
  - Hale, John - 1948 - England - Italian Renaissance History, 1948-1986 (Box 85, Folder 693)
  - Hall, Nigel John - 1967 - England - Sculpture, 1967-1987 (Box 85, Folder 694)
  - Hall, Noel Frederick - 1925 - England - Economics, 1925-1983 (Box 85, Folder 695)
  - Hall, Reginald - 1960 - England - Endocrinology, 1959-1984 (Box 85, Folder 696)
  - Hallam, Anthony - 1963 - England - Geology, 1963-1986 (Box 85, Folder 697)
  - Halliday, John Stuart - 1971 - England - Engineering, 1970-1989 (Box 85, Folder 698)
  - Hamann, Conrad - 1978 - Australia - Art History, 1977-1984 (Box 85, Folder 699)
  - Hamilton, James - 1935 - England - Medicine, 1935-1972 (Box 85, Folder 700)
  - Hamlin, Robert Philip - 1988 - England - Business Administration, 1987-1991 (Box 85, Folder 701)
  - Hampson, George - 1936 - England - Molecular Structure, 1936-1988 (Box 86, Folder 702)
  - Hancock, David - 1965 - England - Economics, 1964-1985 (Box 86, Folder 703)
  - Hancox, Eric - 1934 - England - Geology, 1934-1938 (Box 86, Folder 704)
  - Handy, Nicholas Charles - 1968 - England - Theoretical Chemistry, 1967-1990 (Box 86, Folder 705)
  - Hanotiau, Bernard - 1972 - Belgium - Law, 1972-1987 (Box 86, Folder 706)
  - Hanssen, Hans - 1956 - Norway - American Politics and History, 1955-1976 (Box 86, Folder 707)
  - Harden, Donald - 1926 - England - Archaeology, 1926-1987 (Box 86, Folder 708)
  - Harries, James Ronald - 1958 - England - Cardiopulmonary Physiology, 1957-1980 (Box 86, Folder 709)
  - Harris, John - 1933 - England - Physiology, 1933-1965 (Box 87, Folder 710)
  - Harris, William - 1950 - England - Naval Civil Engineering, 1950-1975 (Box 87, Folder 711)
  - Hart, Stuart - 1962- Australia - Town and Regional Planning, 1962-1983 (Box 87, Folder 712)
  - Hartmann, Klaus - 1953 - Germany - Philosophy, 1953-1984 (Box 87, Folder 713)
  - Harvey, Alexander - 1929 - England - Physics, 1929-1988 (Box 87, Folder 714)
  - Harvey, Jonathan - 1969 - England - Music Cmoposition, 1968-1978 (Box 87, Folder 715)
  - Hatherton, Trevor - 1959 - England - Geophysics, 1958-1985 (Box 87, Folder 716)
  - Haug, Bjorn - 1957 - Norway - Law, 1956-1975 (Box 88, Folder 717)
  - Haug, Walter - 1956 - Switzerland - Comparative Literature and Folklore, 1955-1984 (Box 88, Folder 718)
  - Haughton, Derrick - 1981 - England - Painting, 1980-1988 (Box 88, Folder 719)
  - Haughton, Derrick - 1981 - England - Painting, 1980-1988 (Box 88, Folder 720)
  - Haupt, Peter - 1954 - Germany - Architecture, 1954-1981 (Box 88, Folder 721)
  - Hawking, Ann Phillipa - 1971 - England - Japanese Studies, 1971-1986 (Box 88, Folder 722)
  - Hawking, Ann Phillipa - 1971 - England - Japanese Studies, 1971-1986 (Box 88, Folder 723)
  - Hawkins, Edward Frederick - 1971 - England - Zoology, 1970-1985 (Box 88, Folder 724)
  - Hawthorne, William - 1935 - England - Chemical and Mechanical Engineering, 1935-1988 (Box 89, Folder 725)
  - Hayes, John Trevor - 1958 - England - Art History, 1956-1988 (Box 89, Folder 726)
  - Hayhoe, Thomas - 1978 - England - Business Administration, 1978-1984 (Box 89, Folder 727)
  - Haythornthwaite, Robert - 1950 - England - Structural Engineering, 1949-1980 (Box 89, Folder 728)
  - Hazewinkel, Tjakko - 1961 - Netherlands - Architecture, 1959-1977 (Box 89, Folder 729)
  - Heal, Barbara - 1974 - England - Philosophy and Logic, 1973-1987 (Box 89, Folder 730)
  - Heaton, Ralph - 1951 - England - Denominational Schools in the United States, 1951-1988 (Box 89, Folder 731)
  - Hedley, Barry Davis - 1968 - England - Business Administration, 1967-1988 (Box 89, Folder 732)
  - Heinsch, Harald - 1965 - Germany - Sociology and Political Science, 1964-1967 (Box 90, Folder 733)
  - Heinz, Walter - 1965 - Germany - Social Psychology, 1964-1979 (Box 90, Folder 734)
  - Hemingway, John - 1976 - England - Industrial Relations, 1976-1988 (Box 90, Folder 735)
  - Henderson, George - 1939 - England - Chemistry, 1939-1977 (Box 90, Folder 736)
  - Henderson, Ian William - 1966 - England - Endocrinology, 1966-1983 (Box 90, Folder 737)
  - Henderson, Keith Jefferson - 1954 - England - Political Science, 1954-1986 (Box 90, Folder 738)
  - Henderson, Patrick David - 1952 - England - Economics, 1951-1990 (Box 90, Folder 739)
  - Henderson-Stewart, David James - 1966 - England - Industrial Management, 1966-1990 (Box 91, Folder 740)
  - Henfrey, Colin - 1964 - England - Anthropology, 1963-1986 (Box 91, Folder 741)
  - Henry, Jean Pierre - 1971 - France - Chemistry, 1971-1979 (Box 91, Folder 742)
  - Herding, Richard - 1967 - Germany - Sociology, 1967-1986 (Box 91, Folder 743)
  - Herford, Geoffrey - 1930 - England - Entomology, 1930-1987 (Box 91, Folder 744)
  - Herman, David - 1979 - England - Literature and History, 1978-1990 (Box 91, Folder 745)
  - Herten, Paul - 1968 - Belgium - Law, 1967-1980 (Box 91, Folder 746)
  - Hetherington, Alastair - 1952 - England - American Political History, 1952-1984 (Box 91, Folder 747)
  - Hewer, Thomas - 1927 - England - Pathology, 1927-1987 (Box 92, Folder 748)
  - Hey, Anthony John Grenville - 1970 - England - Physics, 1970-1988 (Box 92, Folder 749)
  - Heyes, Cecilia - 1984 - England - Philosophy of Science, 1983-1988 (Box 92, Folder 750)
  - Heyman, Timothy - 1968 - England - Business Administration, 1967-1989 (Box 92, Folder 751)
  - Hildrew, Peter - 1965 - England - Politics, 1965-1989 (Box 92, Folder 752)
  - Hill, Allan - 1973 - England - Demography, 1972-1987 (Box 92, Folder 753)
  - Hill, Douglas - 1930 - England - Biochemistry, 1930-1987 (Box 93, Folder 754)
  - Hill, Norman - 1932 - England - Electrical Engineering, 1932-1988 (Box 93, Folder 755)
  - Hillis, Arthur - 1950 - England - Public Administration, 1950-1990 (Box 93, Folder 756)
  - Hilton, Ronald - 1937 - England - Spanish and Latin American Studies, 1937-1987 (Box 93, Folder 757)
  - Hilton, Ronald - 1937 - England - Spanish and Latin American Studies, 1937-1987 (Box 93, Folder 758)
  - Hinde, Leonard - 1962 - Australia - Economics, 1962-1987 (Box 93, Folder 759)
  - Hindson, Donald - 1948 - England - Coal Mining Administration, 1948-1989 (Box 94, Folder 760)
  - Hindson, Donald - 1948 - England - Coal Mining Administration, 1948-1989 (Box 94, Folder 761)
  - Hinton, Reginald - 1929 - England - Economics, 1929-1988 (Box 94, Folder 762)
  - Hitchen, Charles - 1931 - England - Economic Geology, 1931-1985 (Box 94, Folder 763)
  - Hoare, David - 1975 - England - Business Administration, 1974-1990 (Box 94, Folder 764)
  - Hobby, Elaine - 1981 - England - English Literature, 1980-1990 (Box 94, Folder 765)
  - Hocker, Hartwig - 1966 - Germany - Polymer Chemistry, 1965-1985 (Box 94, Folder 766)
  - Hodge, Mattew - 1925 - England - Geology, 1925-1954 (Box 94, Folder 767)
  - Hodgkinson, Edith - 1964 - England - East Asian Studies, 1963-1964 (Box 94, Folder 768)
  - Hodgson, Henry - 1935 - Australia - Public Health Engineering, 1934-1985 (Box 95, Folder 769)
  - Hoey, Allan Spencer - 1933 - Australia - Ancient History, 1932-1975 (Box 95, Folder 770)
  - Hofman, Gert - 1965 - Germany - Drama, 1963-1984 (Box 95, Folder 771)
  - Hofmann, Klaus - 1968 - Germany - English and Comparative Literature, 1965-1981 (Box 95, Folder 772)
  - Hofmann, Michael - 1976 - Germany - Sociology, 1975-1984 (Box 95, Folder 773)
  - Hogan, Patrick - 1930 - England - Engineering, 1930-1964 (Box 95, Folder 774)
  - Hogarth, Robin - 1969 - England - Business Administration, 1968-1978 (Box 95, Folder 775)
  - Hogg, Christopher - 1960 - England - Business Administration, 1960-1990 (Box 96, Folder 776)
  - Hollein, Hans - 1958 - Germany - Architecture, 1957-1987 (Box 96, Folder 777)
  - Hollis, James - 1961 - England - Philosophy, 1960-1986 (Box 96, Folder 778)
  - Hollis, James - 1961 - England - Philosophy, 1960-1986 (Box 96, Folder 779)
  - Holmes, David Graham - 1965 - England - Fluid Mechanics, 1964-1985 (Box 96, Folder 780)
  - Holmes, Frank Herbert - 1947 - England - Chemistry, 1947-1975 (Box 96, Folder 781)
  - Holt, David - 1958 - England - Painting, 1957-1987 (Box 96, Folder 782)
  - Holt, David - 1958 - England - Painting, 1957-1987 (Box 96, Folder 783)
  - Honeyman, Alexander - 1932 - England - Literature, 1937-1956 (Box 97, Folder 784)
  - Honeyman, William - 1936 - England - Medicine, 1936-1946 (Box 97, Folder 785)
  - Hoogenberk, Egbert Jan - 1975 - Netherlands - Architecture, 1974-1984 (Box 97, Folder 786)
  - Hoogenberk, Egbert Jan - 1975 - Netherlands - Architecture, 1974-1984 (Box 97, Folder 787)
  - Hooper, Alfred Gifford - 1932 - England - English Literature, 1932-1975 (Box 97, Folder 788)
  - Hooper, Richard - 1966 - England - Educational Technology, 1965-1984 (Box 97, Folder 789)
  - Hope, Francis - 1965 - England - Journalism, 1965-1976 (Box 97, Folder 790)
  - Hope-Jones, Arthur - 1934 - England - Economics and Politics, 1934-1984 (Box 97, Folder 791)
  - Hope-Wallace, Dorothy Jacqueline - 1952 - England - Public Assistance Administration, 1952-1990 (Box 97, Folder 792)
  - Hornby, John Martin - 1965 - England - Economics, 1964-1990 (Box 97, Folder 793)
  - Hornel, James Campbell - 1936 - England - Physical Chemistry, 1936-1975 (Box 98, Folder 794)
  - Hornsby, Timothy - 1961 - England - Political Theory, 1961-1989 (Box 98, Folder 795)
  - Hornsby, Timothy - 1961 - England - Political Theory, 1961-1989 (Box 98, Folder 796)
  - Horwitz, Christopher - 1979 - Australia - Electrical Engineering and Solar Energy, 1978-1983 (Box 98, Folder 797)
  - Houlton, Robert - 1965 - England - Economics and Industrial Relations, 1964-1984 (Box 98, Folder 798)
  - House, Michael Robert - 1958 - England - Paleantology, 1957-1989 (Box 98, Folder 799)
  - Howard, Anthony - 1960 - England - Journalism, 1959-1990 (Box 98, Folder 800)
  - Howard, Brian John - 1970 - England - Chemical Physics, 1969-1986 (Box 99, Folder 801)
  - Howard, Christopher - 1936 - England - History, 1936-1990 (Box 99, Folder 802)
  - Howard, John - 1931 - England - Chemistry, 1931-1935 (Box 99, Folder 803)
  - Howe, Robert - 1956 - England - Entolomogy, 1956-1988 (Box 99, Folder 804)
  - Hudson, Christopher - 1975 - England - English Literature, 1975-1990 (Box 99, Folder 805)
  - Hudson, Frederick Lyth - 1930 - England - Chemistry, 1930-1989 (Box 99, Folder 806)
  - Hudspith, Simon - 1982 - England - Architecture, 1981-1990 (Box 99, Folder 807)
  - Huet, Bernard Yves - 1962 - France - Architecture, 1962-1980 (Box 99, Folder 808)
  - Hughs, Antony - 1967 - England - Physics, 1967-1988 (Box 99, Folder 809)
  - Huibregtse, Johan Wilhelm - 1954 - Netherlands - Economics, 1954-1977 (Box 99, Folder 810)
  - Hulbert, David - 1975 - England - Business Administration, 1975-1986 (Box 100, Folder 811)
  - Hulme, Philip William - 1971 - England - Business Administration, 1970-1987 (Box 100, Folder 812)
  - Hume, Harry Lancelot - 1939 - New Zealand - Civil Engineering, 1939-1981 (Box 100, Folder 813)
  - Humphrey, William Gerald - 1929 - England - Organic Chemistry, 1929-1986 (Box 100, Folder 814)
  - Humphreys, Arthur - 1933 - England - Literature, 1935-1986 (Box 100, Folder 815)
  - Humphreys, John - 1938 - England - History, 1938-1985 (Box 100, Folder 816)
  - Humphreys, Robert - 1930 - England - History, 1930-1987 (Box 100, Folder 817)
  - Humphries, Walter - 1929 - England - Philosophy of Education, 1929-1980 (Box 100, Folder 818)
  - Hunter, John Garvin - 1977 - England - Health Services Administration, 1976-1986 (Box 100, Folder 819)
  - Hunter, Stephen - 1959 - England - Mathematics, 1959-1982 (Box 101, Folder 820)
  - Hurst, Lewis - 1938 - South Africa - Psychiatry, 1937-1975 (Box 101, Folder 821)
  - Husain, Masud - 1987 - England - News Science, 1986-1988 (Box 101, Folder 822)
  - Hutton, Maurice Inglis - 1927 - England - History, 1927-1970 (Box 101, Folder 823)
  - Huxley, Hughes Esmor - 1952 - England - Molecular Biology, 1951-1989 (Box 101, Folder 824)
  - Huxley, Paul - 1965 - England - Painting, 1965-1990 (Box 101, Folder 825)
  - Hyde, Francis - 1931 - England - Economic History, 1931-1980 (Box 101, Folder 826)
  - Hyde, John - 1975 - England - Molecular Biology, 1974-1985 (Box 101, Folder 827)
  - Iest, Karin - 1976 - Netherlands - Law, 1975-1983 (Box 102, Folder 0827A)
  - Inlander, Henry - 1960 - England - Painting, 1960-1984 (Box 102, Folder 828)
  - Innes, James - 1947 - England - Hematology, 1947-1985 (Box 102, Folder 829)
  - Ions, Edmund - 1958 - England - American Government and Politics, 1956-1987 (Box 102, Folder 830)
  - Irving, John - 1930 - Scotland - Geology, 1930-1987 (Box 102, Folder 831)
  - Ivanovici, Angela - 1977 - Australia - Marine Biology, 1976-1987 (Box 102, Folder 832)
  - Iverach, David - 1976 - Australia - Management, 1975-1978 (Box 102, Folder 833)
  - Iversen, Leslie - 1964 - England - Biochemistry, 1964-1987 (Box 103, Folder 834)
  - Ivimy, John - 1950 - England - Business and Industrial Studies, 1950-1984 (Box 103, Folder 835)
  - Jackson, Charles - 1976 - England - Business Administration, 1975-1984 (Box 103, Folder 836)
  - Jackson, Desmond - 1958 - England - Forestry, 1957-1989 (Box 103, Folder 837)
  - Jackson, Fraser - 1965 - New Zealand - Economics, 1964-1975 (Box 103, Folder 838)
  - Jacob, Pierre - 1973 - France - History of Science, 1972-1986 (Box 103, Folder 839)
  - Jacobs, Maxwell - 1939 - Australia - Forestry, 1939-1980 (Box 103, Folder 840)
  - Jaffe, Andrew Michael - 1951 - England - Art History, 1950-1989 (Box 103, Folder 841)
  - James, Gwyn Ingli - 1953 - England - English Literature, 1952-1975 (Box 103, Folder 842)
  - James, Ioan Mackenzie - 1954 - England - Mathematics, 1954-1975 (Box 104, Folder 843)
  - James, Kenneth - 1957 - England - Engineering, 1957-1982 (Box 104, Folder 844)
  - James, Phyllis Bertha Mabel - 1957 - England - Broadcasting, 1957-1986 (Box 104, Folder 845)
  - James, Reginold - 1929 - England - History, 1929-1957 (Box 104, Folder 846)
  - Janson, Philippe - 1972 - Belgium - Computer Science, 1972-1987 (Box 104, Folder 847)
  - Janson, Philippe - 1972 - Belgium - Computer Science, 1972-1987 (Box 104, Folder 848)
  - Janssens, Gerard - 1963 - Netherlands - American Studies, 1963-1975 (Box 104, Folder 849)
  - Jeffcoat, Colin - 1972 - Australia - History, 1972-1986 (Box 104, Folder 850)
  - Jefferson, Timothy - 1981 - England - Paleontology, 1980-1984 (Box 105, Folder 851)
  - Jendges, Hans - 1964 - Germany - Political Science, 1964-1969 (Box 105, Folder 852)
  - Jenkins, Bryan - 1973 - Australia - Engineering, 1972-1987 (Box 105, Folder 853)
  - Jenkins, Daniel - 1948 - England - Theology, 1939-1984 (Box 105, Folder 854)
  - Jenkins, Hywel - 1934 - England - Chemistry, 1934-1972 (Box 105, Folder 855)
  - Jenkins, Peter Redmond - 1971 - England - Literature, 1970-1989 (Box 105, Folder 856)
  - Jepson, Richard - 1951 - England - Experimental Surgery, 1950-1981 (Box 106, Folder 857)
  - Jessell, Thomas Michael - 1977 - England - Neuro-Pharmacology, 1977-1984 (Box 106, Folder 858)
  - Jewell, Nicholas - 1976 - England - Statistics, 1975-1980 (Box 106, Folder 859)
  - Jinks, John - 1959 - England - Genetics, 1959-1987 (Box 106, Folder 860)
  - Johns, Alan Tutton - 1954 - New Zealand - Non-Clinical Biochemistry, 1954-1985 (Box 106, Folder 861)
  - Johnson, Clifford James - 1970 - England - Operations Research and Statistics, 1969-1987 (Box 106, Folder 862)
  - Johnson, David Hugh Nevil - 1948 - England - Law, 1948-1975 (Box 106, Folder 863)
  - Johnson, Martin Hugh - 1970 - England - Reproductive Physiology, 1969-1988 (Box 106, Folder 864)
  - Johnson, Robert Wallace - 1966 - England - Volcanic Geology, 1965-1975 (Box 106, Folder 865)
  - Johnson, Stanley Patrick - 1963 - England - Literature and Drama, 1962-1984 (Box 107, Folder 866)
  - Johnston, Janet Ruth - 1970 - Australia - Social Work, 1970-1985 (Box 107, Folder 867)
  - Johnston, Judith - 1978 - New Zealand - Geography, 1977-1983 (Box 107, Folder 868)
  - Jones, Alexandra - 1983 - England - German Studies, 1982-1988 (Box 107, Folder 869)
  - Jones, Chester Henry - 1927 - England - Architecture, 1927-1938 (Box 107, Folder 870)
  - Jones, Colin Stewart - 1958 - England - Journalism, 1956-1990 (Box 107, Folder 871)
  - Jones, Derek Hugh - 1961 - England - Astronomy, 1961-1981 (Box 107, Folder 872)
  - Jones, Douglas Samuel - 1947 - England - Physics, 1947-1988 (Box 107, Folder 873)
  - Jones, Garth Owen - 1946 - England - Engineering, 1939-1978 (Box 107, Folder 874)
  - Jones, Gomer Llewellyn - 1934 - England - Composition, 1934-1980 (Box 108, Folder 875)
  - Jones, Karen Vanessa - 1988 - England - Flute Studies, 1987-1990 (Box 108, Folder 876)
  - Jones, Maldwyn - 1951 - England - American History, 1950-1983 (Box 108, Folder 877)
  - Jones, Maldwyn - 1951 - England - American History, 1950-1983 (Box 108, Folder 878)
  - Jones, Maxwell - 1936 - England - Medicine, 1936-1986 (Box 108, Folder 879)
  - Jones, Richard Norman - 1937 - England - Chemistry, 1937-1984 (Box 108, Folder 880)
  - Jones, Stephen - 1933 - England - Geology, 1933-1983 (Box 108, Folder 881)
  - Jones, Thomas - 1925 - England - Physics, 1925-1987 (Box 108, Folder 882)
  - Jordan, Denis Oswald - 1948 - Australia - Physical Chemistry, 1948-1982 (Box 108, Folder 883)
  - Jordan, Kenneth - 1969 - England - Public Administration, 1969-1990 (Box 108, Folder 884)
  - Joubert, Christian - 1932 - England - Entomology, 1932-1948 (Box 108, Folder 885)
  - Jouet, Josiane - 1972 - France - Mass Media, 1971-1981 (Box 109, Folder 886)
  - Jouet, Josiane - 1972 - France - Mass Media, 1971-1981 (Box 109, Folder 887)
  - Jukes, John David - 1954 - England - Aeronautical Engineering, 1953-1976 (Box 109, Folder 888)
  - Jupp, Alan Henry - 1969 - England - Celestial Mechanics, 1968-1988 (Box 109, Folder 889)
  - Karia, Chirag - 1989 - England - Law, 1988-1989 (Box 109, Folder 890)
  - Kean, Arnold - 1936 - England - Law, 1936-1989 (Box 109, Folder 891)
  - Keane, John Patrick - 1946 - England - Economics and Government, 1939-1988 (Box 109, Folder 892)
  - Keatley, Mark Burgess - 1984 - England - Business Administration, 1983-1990 (Box 109, Folder 893)
  - Keelan, Hugh - 1979 - England - Music, 1978-1987 (Box 110, Folder 894)
  - Keith, John - 1966 - England - English Literature, 1965-1987 (Box 110, Folder 895)
  - Kekwick, Ralph - 1931 - England - Physical Biochemistry, 1931-1988 (Box 110, Folder 896)
  - Kellar, Alexander - 1928 - England - Law, 1928-1984 (Box 110, Folder 897)
  - Keller, Ulrich - 1969 - Germany - English Literature, 1967-1986 (Box 110, Folder 898)
  - Kelly, Lindsay David - 1971 - Australia - City Planning, 1969-1975 (Box 110, Folder 899)
  - Kelly, Thomas - 1930 - England - Economics, 1930-1983 (Box 110, Folder 900)
  - Kemball, Charles - 1946 - England - Chemistry, 1946-1990 (Box 110, Folder 901)
  - Kemp, Brian Richard Calvert - 1970 - England - Business Administration, 1969-1989 (Box 111, Folder 902)
  - Kendall, Bridget - 1978 - England - Soviet Studies, 1977-1989 (Box 111, Folder 903)
  - Kendall, Christopher - 1965 - England - Geology, 1965-1985 (Box 111, Folder 904)
  - Kennedy, Robert Keith Milroy - 1966 - England - Business Administration, 1965-1990 (Box 111, Folder 905)
  - Kent, Leslie - 1950 - England - Engineering Geology, 1950-1985 (Box 111, Folder 906)
  - Kent, Leslie - 1950 - England - Engineering Geology, 1950-1985 (Box 111, Folder 907)
  - Kerr, Karl - 1927 - Ireland - Chemistry, 1927-1969 (Box 111, Folder 908)
  - Kerrison, Bernard Edward - 1970 - England - Business Administration, 1970-1986 (Box 111, Folder 909)
  - Kessler, Didier - 1973 - France - Business Administration, 1972-1987 (Box 112, Folder 910)
  - Kettle, Arnold - 1939 - England - English, 1939-1987 (Box 112, Folder 911)
  - Keuning, Roelof - 1960 - Netherlands - Physics, 1960-1984 (Box 112, Folder 912)
  - Kibble, Thomas - 1958 - England - Physics, 1957-1979 (Box 112, Folder 913)
  - Kidd, Richard - 1980 - England - Painting, 1979-1988 (Box 112, Folder 914)
  - Kidd, Timothy - 1969 - England - Literature and Drama, 1968-1975 (Box 112, Folder 915)
  - Kimber, Hugh - 1956 - Australia - Engineering, 1956-1975 (Box 112, Folder 916)
  - Kingi, Pauline - 1983 - New Zealand - Law, 1982-1985 (Box 112, Folder 917)
  - Kinsey, Bernard Bruno - 1933 - England - Physics, 1933-1975 (Box 112, Folder 918)
  - Kirsh, Mark William - 1988 - England - Law, 1987-1991 (Box 113, Folder 919)
  - Kirchner, Christian - 1971 - Germany - Law and Economics, 1970-1985 (Box 113, Folder 920)
  - Kirk, Geoffrey - 1949 - England - Classics, 1949-1987 (Box 113, Folder 921)
  - Kirk, John Henry - 1932 - England - Inter-Racial Sociology, 1932-1988 (Box 113, Folder 922)
  - Kirk, Stuart Raeburn - 1925 - England - Geology, 1925-1934 (Box 113, Folder 923)
  - Kirk-Greene, Anthony - 1958 - England - African Studies, 1958-1988 (Box 113, Folder 924)
  - Kirkland, Andrew - 1969 - New Zealand - Forestry, 1969-1987 (Box 113, Folder 925)
  - Kirkwood, Henrietta - 1952 - New Zealand - Education, 1951-1986 (Box 113, Folder 926)
  - Kitcherm, Philip Stuart - 1969 - England - Philosophy of Science, 1969-1973 (Box 114, Folder 927)
  - Kitching, John - 1958 - England - Business Administration, 1957-1984 (Box 114, Folder 928)
  - Kitshoff, Johannes - 1953 - South Africa - Economics, 1953-1990 (Box 114, Folder 929)
  - Klabbers, Jan - 1968 - Netherlands - Systems Psychology, 1967-1985 (Box 114, Folder 930)
  - Klemperer, Paul - 1980 - England - Business Administration, 1979-1990 (Box 114, Folder 931)
  - Kliskey, Philip Roberts - 1954 - England - Engineering, 1953-1985 (Box 114, Folder 932)
  - Kloeke, Willem Van Lessen - 1967 - Netherlands - Linguistics, 1967-1984 (Box 115, Folder 933)
  - Knight, Margaret Madeline - 1964 - England - Social Work, 1963-1973 (Box 115, Folder 934)
  - Knowles, Henry Robert - 1931 - England - Agriculture, 1931-1960 (Box 115, Folder 935)
  - Knox, Colin - 1981 - New Zealand - Public Administration, 1981-1986 (Box 115, Folder 936)
  - Kogan, Maurice - 1960 - England - Educational Administration, 1959-1976 (Box 115, Folder 937)
  - Koehne, Graeme John - 1984 - Australia - Music, 1984-1987 (Box 115, Folder 938)
  - Kompa, Karl Ludwig - 1965 - Germany - Physical Chemistry, 1964-1980 (Box 115, Folder 939)
  - Kooiman, Jan - 1963 - Netherlands - Public Administration, 1963-1987 (Box 115, Folder 940)
  - Koolhaas, Remment - 1972 - Netherlands - Urban Design, 1971-1980 (Box 115, Folder 941)
  - Koolhaas, Teun - 1967 - Netherlands - Architecture, 1967-1980 (Box 116, Folder 942)
  - Koritz, Andor - 1965 - Germany - Foreign Aid Administration, 1964-1983 (Box 116, Folder 943)
  - Kornberg, Hans Leo - 1953 - Germany - Biochemistry, 1953-1988 (Box 116, Folder 944)
  - Kroes, Rob - 1968 - Netherlands - Sociology, 1967-1975 (Box 116, Folder 945)
  - Kruijtbosch, Egbert - 1957 - Netherlands - Economics, 1956-1975 (Box 116, Folder 946)
  - Kruyt, Gerdina Johanna - 1971 - Netherlands - Statistics, 1970-1984 (Box 116, Folder 947)
  - Kuhn, Robert - 1980 - Australia - Mathematics, 1979-1985 (Box 116, Folder 948)
  - Kuipers, Abele - 1976 - Netherlands - Animal Husbandry, 1975-1987 (Box 117, Folder 949)
  - Kupers, Fritz - 1956 - Netherlands - Economics, 1955-1987 (Box 117, Folder 950)
  - Labin, Hans-Peter - 1967 - Germany - Banking and International Affairs, 1966-1984 (Box 117, Folder 951)